I'll take the heart-smart platter.
All right, thank you. And Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)We don't eat here.
I don't know what's good.
- Well, it's all good.
- Statistically unlikely.
(Leonard:)Just get a hamburger.
You like hamburgers.
(Sheldon:)I like the hamburgers
where we usually eat.
(Sheldon:)You can't make the assumption
that I'll like the hamburgers here.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry. Give him a hamburger.
(Penny:)Which one,
the classic, the ranch house...
...the barbeque burger
or the Kobe burger?
(Sheldon:)Can't we just go to Big Boy?
(Sheldon:)- They only have one burger, the Big Boy.
- The barbeque burger's like the Big Boy.
(Sheldon:)In a world that already
includes a Big Boy...
(Sheldon:)...why would I settle for something
like a Big Boy?
(Penny:)Because you are not at Big Boy.
- Fine. I'll have the barbeque burger.
- Make it two.
(Sheldon:)Waitresses don't yell at you at Big Boy.
(Lesley(entering):)Hey, Leonard. Hi, guys.
(Penny:)- Hey.
- Hey, Leslie.
- I didn't know you ate here.
- We don't. This is a disturbing aberration.
Leslie, this is Penny, she lives across
the hall from Sheldon and me.
(Howard:)And walks in quiet beauty
like the night.